[music]
>> I want to buy a new car.
>> [music]
>> I want to buy a new shoe on my birthday.
>> Which one is the best of all?
>> [music]
>> I'm so good, guys.
[music]
>> No, it's a combination, but I'll show
you.
I want them to go down in
>> [music]
>> history as the best year of my life.
>> Yes.
>> I swear to God.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's
9:00. It's actually almost 9:00 p.m. I
just started food because I've had a
really long day.
over the whole day, but this cold season
is usually just a bit too much for me.
That's why I'm even wearing this robe. I
don't wear a robe outside. I usually use
this robe when it's extremely cold. Uh I
ordered pizza. Chicken is on the way.
I'll show you. We're about to go to the
kitchen in a few. And yeah, that's our
package alarm, but we're going to unbox
it tomorrow. I just want to eat, chill,
and go straight to bed, and probably
watch an episode of Law & Order. I'm
watching Law & Order, the main one, the
original one, the first one, yeah. So,
I'm starting off new vlog. This is the
first time I picked up my camera since I
came back from Zanzibar. I had the most
wonderful trip ever. This has been the
best birthday. I'm so grateful I get to
live the life that I live. That trip
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
[music and singing]
>> Good morning. Today's on Wednesday. But
at least weekly vlog with the mans, I'm
happy. I'm going to the gym. I just want
to show you guys my outfit.
Yeah, I need to hurry up and go back.
Actually, I need to go back. I need to
hurry but we really need to go back cuz
I'm not going to the gym in a really
long time. So, I need to hurry and go to
the gym and then I'll come back and
unbox the lamp. Vlogs are going to be so
much better. Now, I made you a promise.
I told myself if I get an iPad if I get
the iPad that I wanted, I'm going to be
really consistent especially on YouTube
because that's what I use to edit. And
yeah, we're so back.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I just came back
>> from the gym. I'm officially back at the
gym. I didn't remember to change my
angle.
And my body to look as hot as it has
ever been. Because in October
I want to be the hottest I've ever been.
Not even in December.
In October.
>> We got a good thing. Don't know if I'mma
see you
>> I was supposed to do my makeup. Ah.
And at least you could have left me a
chair.
You guys remember I was supposed to do
my makeup?
What happened to the chair? So I was not
able to do my makeup.
I'm wearing a basic outfit, but I had to
show up. I was too tired. It's my first
day back at the gym, so
yeah, it was a bit hard. Let me show you
guys my outfit.
This is what I'm wearing. I'm wearing
this sporty sweater. I'm wearing jeans,
heels, a bag, and I've carried a jacket.
I'm only here for 1 hour,
and then I go home because I have to be
at the gym tomorrow.
>> again,
but is that a good thing? [singing]
Cuz girl, I can't be your [music] man.
No, ma'am. I know what's on your brain.
You're probably hoping never would end.
Like, is it the real thing?
[singing and music]
Or is it just a one-night stand?
Well, then, let me see you get
>> Today is Sunday, the 16th of July. I
just came back from the gym. I was not
able to vlog in the morning. I was too
tired. Went out to the club yesterday,
but thank God I didn't drink, so I was
able to wake up and go to the gym. I
just received some of the things that I
ordered from Jumia, and I want us to
unbox them.
Okay. Wait. This is not what I ordered.
This is not what I ordered. Eh. Oh,
actually it is. Yeah, it is what I
ordered.
I thought it was not what I had ordered,
but now it is. Even it just looked a bit
smaller.
I chose for the cheapest option.
Not really cheap. It's expensive. I
don't know whether this one will work
with my iPad, but it's this SD card
reader. I should probably get a good
quality one. I think now I should buy a
tutor who can teach me how to use it in
person. But, I'm going to try it and see
if it works because I want to stop using
my camera to transfer footage. It takes
a lot of time. And when I'm transferring
footage, I'm not able to vlog. That was
body oil because I saw it was on offer,
and I wanted a body oil. This is a brand
that I have never used. I've actually
never even seen this brand before. Dr.
Dermis vitamin C deep white moisturizing
oil. I just wanted a body oil because I
love glowing, especially when
my legs are out. Boxers shorts that you
guys see me wear all the time. I love
them. I told you guys now
and they're so cute, but they're for
men.
I'm going to wrap here.
I'm going to wear the same colors I had
last time. They're usually really
comfortable. Sometimes you know
how to feed last time. So, these are the
colors that are available.
This is usually my favorite color, and
then we have this one.
We have this. This probably my least
favorite one. It's boring. I love bright
colors. Remember this box that has been
in my house
for a while now.
And this lamp
So, this is what the lamp looks like.
It's a cute
pretty simple and another
This is how it looks. I'm thinking I
should probably put it in my bedroom
because I already have a lamp in the
living room. Now, I want to show you
guys
>> [music and singing]
>> I feel like every time you guys have
seen me this week, I've just been going
to the gym or just back from the gym.
Again, I'm going to the gym right now. I
want to show you guys my outfit.
I'm wearing this shorts that I got from
this babe who sells this really cute gym
sets on Instagram. This jacket that I
got from Heat.
that I have not unboxed. I'm thinking of
unboxing it you guys now.
And I've been wanting new perfumes
Guys, I've run out of all my favorite
perfumes. Yeah, we'll unbox them
together when I'm back. Open this one
and use it
right now.
I love it. I'm not going to do too much
unless I start to upper. Oops, let me
spray cologne upper.
And cologne kidogo just a bit.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
[music and singing]
>> Hi guys, today's on Saturday. I'm going
to the gym again. Actually, the only
reason I'm going to the gym today is
because I won't be able to go to the gym
on Monday. Remember I go to the gym at
least five days a week.
But since I can't go on Monday
So, I'll just go to the gym today. And
I'm wearing this cute gym fit.
I don't know how I'm feeling. I'm not
feeling my best today.
dress up for the gym and go workout.
I'll probably feel better, so I'm hoping
that when I come back home
I'll come back home feeling better. I
think it's also because my periods are
about to come. I'm now going to feel
moody moody. It's supposed to come in
today, I think actually.
Yeah.
I need to check my calendar, but I think
it's today.
Hit. Again, this is where I got the
jacket that I was wearing yesterday.
They sent me a pair of package a few
months back and I love love love love
the quality of the gym wear. I ordered
the samosas from
Samosa World Kenya. I've been seeing
them on TikTok and I saw them in the
Jibu and I saw they were on Uber Eats.
So I ordered the 10 pack, the chili one.
This is me and the 10 pieces and then I
also got these two.
The samosas they are ready to eat now.
I'll probably just warm them and have
them.
Let me scare them you know, but these
ones I got the pre-cooked ones because I
want to be frying them myself.
Nice and okay. So I'm going to put these
ones in the freezer.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> Hey,
I've been waiting for [singing]
>> night for this moment. I've [music] been
waiting all year for this moment. I've
been picturing you taking off your
clothes for me. I've been literally
curving all these [music] songs for you.
Daddy told you better bring your ass
home.
>> [music]
>> Little mama better get [singing] your
ass home.
Baby, I swear these [\h__\h] just don't
understand.
You ain't got [music] to be [singing]
old to be a man.
Take my hand.
>> I'm about to head to the gym. Again, I
got my hair done yesterday.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I've just gotten my package from Ship
Society.
The package has my Bella Barnett outfit.
So, I got one Actually, even one outfit.
This is a two-piece, so that's two. And
then, I don't remember this other two.
But, I'll do the unboxing with you guys
when I'm trying them on. And I'm
supposed to film
Also, I need to find a filming space.
We'll figure it out together. Treasure.
>> [music]
>> Going to be a good birthday.
Uh-huh. What time?
Uh-uh.
But, they
Oh.
>> Good morning, guys. I'm leaving my
edges. I've showered and I'm ready for
the gym. I'm just wearing a robe. I
don't know what studs my party studs
are. Yeah.
I'm just going to wear my old studs and
get ready and go to the gym.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm showered and I've changed into these
cute pajamas that I want to show you
now, papa.
Period is almost here, so I've also
started breaking out. I'm using this I
usually break out every single month,
but
once in a while I do. I'm also
transferring footage for the Zanzibar
vlog, my birthday vlog part two. I
posted part one on Monday. So, I want to
post that one on Sunday or Monday again.
I really love the engagement that I've
been getting.
>> [music]
>> One package has arrived. There's
supposed to be another package cuz I've
confirmed and this is not everything I
had ordered, but I also got heels that
I'm so excited to try out. I hope
they're comfortable. I don't know how
comfortable
their heels are cuz I've never worn
their heels. Let me just show you how
They look it. It's so cute.
Yeah, you see that?
And this is one of the heels that I got.
And then let me show you the black ones.
This is the other pair that I got. It's
a simple black heel. I don't have a lot
of black heels, so I just wanted a
simple black heel that I can wear as an
everyday heel.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> I'm sure you're about to leave. I'm
heading for Leslie's birthday brunch. I
did my makeup. I think I look so cute.
I unboxed that I've been using all week,
which is so good. I've been getting so
many compliments on that perfume. So, I
want to unbox the second one. I hope it
smells good.
And then come out here,
the LV something.
Yeah.
I think it's the one.
Oh, it's so cute. This is how you open
it.
Oh, wow. The packaging is
so cute.
Oh, I like that.
It's cute and simple. You know how it
comes with the other you to buy other LV
one.
Mhm.
I like it. It's more of a fresh scent.
Let me get the other one. Let me use the
other one. I like the other one more.
Uh-huh.
>> You know you know Celine, is it like a
cute spot for wearing a shorts
two piece?
>> The two piece?
And switch to video call
but you can figure when you're taking
pictures you'll just take it off. I like
it.
Bye. Love you.
I'm carrying my pink bag because I feel
like it matches the outfit.
But I'm wearing the black heels that I
got from Fashion Nova. I'm wearing the
leggings. This is actually a two piece
but I want to wear
I wanted to wear this shirt because it's
colorful and the place we're going to is
giving out the same vibes and I just
wanted to wear this shirt today and then
I'm going to hide you this bag and
remember
any my jewelry. Most of them are from
Shein but this is my watch from Pascal.
These
actually and then these earrings that I
got from Pacaya Josie.
>> [music]
[singing]
>> Just got my other Fashion Nova package.
I'm about to open it up and see what's
inside.
I ended up changing my outfit which is
also from Fashion Nova. It's a really
sexy dress. So we have this bag.
Love love love it. That's the first
thing I want us to unbox.
That's a cute bag for this outfit. I was
thinking of carrying my big bag actually
when put everything in here. It's making
my outfit look formal. It's not giving
brunch anymore. Okay, let me see.
Mhm.
>> [music]
>> The outfit makes so much sense.
And the shoes that I need to wear
How do I open? Oh, so it's like a clip.
This is the interior compartment. It's
really cute. I like it.
I really don't know what I want to do
with my hair. I need to clean that up.
So, this is the bag and then
they also sent over these heels that I
am obsessed with. I actually wanted to
wear these heels today with this outfit.
But I think I'm just going to wear the
Fashion Nova heels. But you see these
new heels, the animal print, and you can
actually feel the
And I can't wait
to rock them.
All the things are going to be linked in
the description. Do you guys see that?
Do you guys see? I wear the shoes you
guys are definitely going to see, but
for today
the bag goes with me. So, yeah.
Okay, let's go.
>> [music]
[music]
>> My Uber driver was trying to scam me.
750 bob on top of what I was paying him.
So mad. Thank god I checked.
I really hate people who try to scam me.
Like I didn't even know he was tipping
me.
But now I was like I'm not even going to
tip you.
>> [music]
>> Not trying to waste.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Imagine I was by myself solo drinking.
>> Two glasses. Two.
It's so cute.
>> [music]
>> Can I get
>> Here you go.
How's your meal? I mean everything is
good.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Say hi.
>> Hi.
>> [music]
[music]
>> When you want to get drunk immediately
without wasting time
You know Long Island, literally.
>> Polaris.
>> Yes, I got a Long Island.
>> [music]
>> Such a really cute picture. Now let's do
one hour.
They're just taking pictures doing
nothing. It's fine. I'm going to tell
them we are able to take pictures.
And the
cocktail is hitting.
I'm recording Leslie.
I'm recording how I feel now.
I'm going to cut video guys. I wish you
both be happy.
I cut this video guys.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Thank you.
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> Happy birthday.
>> I love you. I love you guys.
This is the best season in the whole
world.
>> [music]
[laughter]
[music]
>> Happy birthday.
>> [laughter]
[singing]
>> We are going home. Best night ever.
Thank you God for the blessings.
Be grateful.
Kidogo tu yenye umepata.
Exactly.
Hi. How are you? [music]
Hi Sasa.
Hi. See you.
>> [music]
>> Good morning. I'm heading to the gym
because I didn't go to the gym
yesterday. Actually, I just wanted to
give you guys an update. And then when I
come back, I need to shower and get
ready. Not specifically get ready, but
Tanasha is coming over. She's coming to
chill.
And yeah, I'll probably vlog that or
not. I don't know. We'll see. Tuesday,
we are going on a girls staycation. I'm
so excited. Life is really good at the
moment.
Then life is really good for us at the
moment and I am so grateful. I hope God
knows.
Hi guys, I just came back from the gym.
I'm so tired. I didn't even take a I
didn't even go and then I went to the
stair master for 10 minutes. And then I
stretch like I stretch I stretch really
so that I can be able to sleep through
this week and next week is going to be
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> I'm so tired and I'm so ready for next
week.
I'm in a really good space.
Like a really really good space. For the
first time in my life like I can say I'm
really really happy with where I am. And
funny thing is it's not at kuna to make
a funny guy like there's nothing. My
life has not changed.
Sadly, but we'll buy it. Amen. Soon, I
pray and hope. Like we don't want to
have a major shift in the December and
happy because this has happened. Not
really good place.
I was just watching KM story and I'm a
post a vlog. So, that's my plan for now.
>> I kind of pour into my cup.
>> I spoken to tea and she's not able to
make it today. So, we've moved our date
to next week Friday. Now, I got to be
thinking with adulting like I just want
to show you guys
this outfit that I wanted to wear. It's
a pajama from Fashion Nova. Now, I see
me going to enjoy me shorts.
And like a bra top and a robe. This is
the top. I thought this was shorts, but
actually you need to come out there like
boy shorts. Yeah, if that makes sense.
Literally you can have two panties. And
then, thank god it has a robe. But it
was really near cooker in the bus. So,
I'm not going anywhere. No one is going
to see me. So, it's fine. This cute
wallpaper that I found and I really love
having wallpapers especially if I'm not
watching TV. So, I can be cooking with
blood like every time I walk I pass by
my living room. Most times I'm usually
just in my room. I can have a corner
even like a beautiful background. And
yeah, I love it. It's so cute. I'm
transferring footage the vlog that I'm
supposed to edit. And I was just
watching like the clips and bits of the
vlog and I realized I didn't have to be
the one who planned my birthday and I
didn't have to be the one who made [\h__\h]
happen on my birthday. And it felt
really good because I can't even tell
you how happy I was in the moment.
And I can just feel myself bursting with
happiness because of how happy I was.
>> [music]
>> Hi guys. So, it's 1:29. Actually, it's
1:30 a.m.
And this is the time I'm done editing
the vlog. So, I'm uploading it.
And I'm going straight to bed. I have to
go to the gym tomorrow morning. And I
need to get my hair done as well.
I just have a long week ahead.
But at least you guys are getting the
birthday vlog in time. You know the
other one again now
was posted 6 days ago. So you're getting
the vlog exactly after a week. I'm so
proud of myself, Lonnie.
Okay, good night. I'll see you guys in
the morning.
Good morning. I was able to wake up for
the gym. I just want to rush and go to
the gym. I'll speak to you guys once I'm
back because I have a hair appointment.
I'm wearing just a basic
outfit which I'm wearing now.
I'm wearing a basic outfit. I'm wearing
this jacket and I'm wearing this romper
and my sneakers
and my black bag. Let me go and then
come back and we'll speak. I'm supposed
to get my hair done. I'm actually going
to go and cut these braids so that I can
get a wig installed. After's birthday is
tomorrow.
Be ready for fire content, Lonnie.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Love me. I love it. It looks so good. It
always looks so good every time you
install [music] my hair.
>> [music]
>> I I'm so excited for tomorrow already.
Now plus I'm taking advantage of that to
film my Fashion Nova deliverables and
also have a brand that I'm working with
Bella Barnett. They sent me my clothes
recently, but I've not been able to
shoot. So, I also want to try the Bella
Barnett pieces and go with them.
With you guys out together, we buy our
of my followers on Instagram she just
texted me and told me she wants to get
me a cake because she knows I love this
particular cake. Salted caramel. A funny
thing about the cake I give for
everybody. If you're not a sweet tooth,
it's probably not the cake for you, but
I love it cuz I especially love ziwa.
And then we also have the salted
caramel.
I have no idea why. These are the two
go-to flavors. And then we also have the
salted caramel.
Each slice here white rose in a cup
cooler. This is the salted caramel and
then any white chocolate rose in a warm
beer.
Good morning. I woke up a bit late Leo,
but I've been in bed, I've been working,
I've been editing, I've been doing a few
things. You can imagine the weather and
the lighting is not so good.
So, I just received this package from
Zari.
It's your birthday so definitely we're
going to drink as much as we can with
us.
I'm probably going to pack this. I want
to pack
Now, I'm going to need to figure out how
to pack the main important outfit that I
need is the going out club outfit that
I'm going to wear
today.
I don't know. We'll see. Here's my
suitcase. I want to take the tiny
suitcase with me. I'm going to get the
other one. I'm going to get the other
smaller one. I need to take one suitcase
and pack things. Look at all my PR
packages and my Fashion Nova. I need to
pick a few outfits from here that I will
carry with me. Actually, I think I'll
take baby Fashion Nova with me. I think
I'm probably going to carry one Fashion
Nova outfit and then Bella Barnett.
Those are the outfits I want to carry. I
just want to
pack a few things real quick and then we
go. Yeah.
Right, so short. It's supposed to be a
skirt.
I didn't know it was a three piece. It
actually has stockings. I just thought
it was a two piece, but I'll probably
not need the stockings for tonight. You
turn it up.
I'm ready yet. I'm dressed and ready to
leave. I'm actually just wearing a basic
outfit and I want to wear this like let
me show you.
I want to wear this pink side they're so
cute. Also I got
them for me. I got them as a birthday
gift this year. I don't even know what
my birthday gift is. Let me open up to
eat package and then I saw this slippers
and I thought they were so cute. I'm
carrying my pink bag.
My tripod, obviously you guys know
I'm going to work work on this creator
and then I have my suitcase that I will
line coming up and then the sweatpants
are from Shein and my pink bag to mix
these two perfumes. If you want to know
how much I love this perfume, I've had
this one for months and I've only had
this one for a month, less than a month.
>> [music]
>> Let me take a few pictures for the gram
and then yeah, I'll see you guys.
I'm here.
And I'm on the second floor.
>> [music]
>> This is the This is the fattest body.
Oh, the house is beautiful.
Oh, hey.
Guys, I just want to show you a simple
overview of the hospital. Yeah, you
cute. You are orange and you cute.
Oh, it looks nice.
>> And come to my house.
>> The bathroom.
>> This is where the queen will be
sleeping.
This is where the queen will be
Uh
>> The princess.
>> The birthday girl.
>> Ambassador of the ghetto.
>> Oh, I can see beautiful.
We are just going to go to the club.
Club.
>> [laughter]
>> to buy a new shoes on my birthday.
>> Guys, 10 minutes room. I unpack a few
things.
And then
We just have to chill by the
balcony.
>> Again.
Cuz once again he's [music] out
doing wrong and my girls are so real.
Said it's been a minute since I last
>> Ooh. [music]
>> See, you won't be the only one. Just
want [music] to ask one That's when you
put it on. Get them up tight. This is
your song. I've got your back. I'm the
empress. Pull out your break the mass.
>> [music]
>> Put your break the mass.
Put your break the mass.
>> [singing]
>> Put your break the mass.
Put your break the mass.
>> [music]
[music]
>> This is one of my favorite years ever.
It's going to go down in history as the
best year of my life.
>> Yes.
>> I swear to God.
>> There's more coming.
>> TONIGHT
>> WHAT ARE YOU NEED?
SO COOL.
>> You have to suck all.
pink red
Nico pink red
red red
Oh, that's so cute.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Nothing else.
>> [laughter]
[music and singing]
[music]
[singing]
>> They're having a blast and to shower.
They're about to start getting ready for
the club.
>> [singing and music]
[music]
>> Cuz cuz being [singing] your friend
>> [music]
>> is killing me softly.
Your voice is
>> [music]
>> Baby, I know you mean
probably going to save me.
>> In the wrong [singing] time.
I wonder so often
>> [music]
>> we could have
Don't compare
>> [music]
>> at all.
Oh.
My
ex best,
all they do is distract
[music and singing] me for now.
Deep down, when I face it, all [singing]
I want is [music] you.
Ooh.
All I want is you.
>> [music]